var
    questions = [{
        "question": "WHAT WAS THE FIRST FEATURE-LENGTH ANIMATED MOVIE EVER RELEASED?",
        "option1": "Fantasias",
        "option2": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
        "option3": "An Steamboat Willie",
        "option4": "Dumbo",
        "answer": "2"
}, {
        "question": "WHAT IS THE HIGHEST GROSSING MOVIE OF ALL TIME??",
        "option1": "Avengers: Endgame",
        "option2": "Titanic",
        "option3": "Avatar",
        "option4": "Cruella",
        "answer": "3"
}, {
        "question": "SEBASTIAN, SCUTTLE, AND FLOUNDER ARE ALL CHARACTERS IN WHAT ANIMATED FILM?",
        "option1": "The Little Mermaid",
        "option2": "Finding Nemo",
        "option3": "Frozen",
        "option4": "The Lion King",
        "answer": "1"
}, {
        "question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CHARACTER PLAYED BY JENNIFER LAWRENCE IN THE HUNGER GAMES?",
        "option1": "Primrose Everdeen",
        "option2": "Effie Trinket",
        "option3": "Katnis Everdeen",
        "option4": "Peeta Mellark ",
        "answer": "3"
}, {
        "question": "WHICH DISNEY PRINCESS DRESSES UP AS A MAN TO SAVE HER FATHER?",
        "option1": "Ariel",
        "option2": "Merida",
        "option3": "Cindarella",
        "option4": "Mulan",
        "answer": "4"
}, {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct famous dialogue of the evil queen from Snow White?",
        "option1": "Mirror mirror on the wall who`s the fairest of them all",
        "option2": " Mirror mirror on the wall who`s the fairest one of all?",
        "option3": "Mirror mirror on the wall who`s fairest out of all?",
        "option4": "Mirror mirror on the wall who`s fairest of them all?",
        "answer": "2"
}, {
        "question": "From which platform at Kings Cross the Hogwarts Express train depart?",
        "option1": "Platform Seven and two-quarters",
        "option2": "Platform Wand",
        "option3": "Nine and three-quarters",
        "option4": "Platform 5",
        "answer": "3"
}, {
        "question": "What female character in the Spider-Verse is also bitten by a radioactive spider and becomes Spider-Woman??",
        "option1": "Mary Jane Watson.",
        "option2": "Aunt May ",
        "option3": "Jessica Drew ", 
        "option4": "Gwen Stacy",
        "answer": "4"
}, {
        "question": "What was the name of Maleficient`s pet raven, in Sleeping Beauty?",
        "option1": "Diablo",
        "option2": "Diable",
        "option3": "Mauvais",
        "option4": "Malcolm",
        "answer": "1"
}, {
        "question": "What`s the term for non-magical people  ?",
        "option1": "Dentists ",
        "option2": "Wizards",
        "option3": "Muggles",
        "option4": "Gryffs",
        "answer": "3"
}];
